

CONTACTS

(+95) 9-966680686

chitoonaung.ts@gmail.com

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth September 7, 1998

> Gender Male

Website chitoonaung.com

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/chit-oo-naung

github.com/Chit-Oo-Naung

LANGUAGES

0 0 0 0

Burmese (native)

English

Japanese

Chit Oo Naung

Full Stack Developer

WORK EXPERIENCES

Myanmar Information Technology Co., Ltd. (MIT)

Team Lead (Software IT), Apr 2018 - Jan 2023

- Team Management
- Develop Code
- Test, deploy and monitor applications
- Manage UI/UX design for applications
- Work with team for designing the database system
- Write document for product
- Solve customer issues

TASTYSOFT Software Outsourcing Co., Ltd.

Senior Software Developer & Trainer, Feb 2014 – Jan 2023

- Manage all team members
- Meet with customer (project owner)
- Trainer of technologies and tools

SKILLS

- Dart
- Python
- HTML
- css/scss

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Node.js

FRAMEWORKS

- Flutter
- Ionic
- Angular

- Bootstrap
- Tailwind
- Flask

FAMILIAR CLOUD SERVICES

- AWS Digital Ocean
- Azure

Summary

Have 7+ years' experience in Web and Mobile development.

Experience in Android SDK, Xcode, Frameworks, third libraries, Git and APIs.

Have experience in published application at Play Store and App Store.

Good skill in Coding, debugging, testing, and troubleshooting.

Eager to learn new technologies and tools.

Good communication, Hardworking and Honestly Candidate.

EDUCATION

High School Diploma 2013-2014

Mogok High School Kyatpyin

Bachelor of Art (Geography) 2019

Mandalay Yadanabon University

ACTIVITIES

Saw Saw Shar 2019

Help as Mobile Developer for Covid-19 contact tracing application platform

Organized by Myanmar Computer Federation (MCF)

SE2022 Software Engineer Contest

Help as Mentor for Second Prize Winner Team (LazySoft)

Organized by Ko Zin Min and Ko Htain Lin Shwe

PROJECT EXPERIENCES

1. Human Resource Management System

Position: Team Lead

Technology Used: Angular (Web), Flutter (Mobile), Python

(APIs), DynamoDB (Database)

3. E-Learning Platform

Position : Team Lead

Technology Used: Angular (Web), Flutter (Mobile), Python

(APIs), DynamoDB (Database)

2. Taxi Driver and Admin Panel

Position: Team Lead

Technology Used: Angular (Web), Flutter (Mobile), Python

(APIs), PostgreSQL (Database)

4. Coupon Management System

Position: Team Lead

Technology Used : Angular (Web), Flutter (Mobile), Python

(APIs), DynamoDB (Database)

5. Banking UI

Position: Developer

Technology Used: Angular (Web), Flutter (Mobile)

6. Human Resource Management System

Position : Developer

Technology Used : Angular (Web), Ionic 3 (Mobile),

Java/Tomcat (APIs), MS SQL (Database)

5. Delivery, Surveyor, Retailer

Position: Developer

Technology Used: Angular (Web), Ionic 3 (Mobile),

Java/Tomcat (APIs), SQL (Database)

8. School Management System (Desktop)

Position: Developer

Technology Used: C#, MS SQL (Database)

9. Gold Shop POS (Desktop)

Position: Developer

Technology Used: C#, MS SQL (Database)